<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SecureYou</string>
    <string name="key_name">name</string>
    <string name="titleimage">TitleImage</string>
    <string name="start_button">Start Button</string>
    <string name="persons_name">Persons name</string>
    <string name="storyImage">StoryImage</string>

    <string name="page0">You check your phone, it says 16:55. You just
        finished a tough project and are excited to get home for the day.
        While getting ready to leave the office, you check your email and
        see there is something new in your inbox that looks to be from
        someone in upper management.</string>
    <string name="page0_choice1">Open the new email</string>
    <string name="page0_choice2">Go home and deal with it later</string>

    <string name="page1">You open the email and it reads, \n
        "Dear %1$s, \n \n
        It has come to our attention that the system that stores employee
        information requires an update so you will need to enter
        your login information into the linked form at the bottom
        of the email so that the system can be updated with your
        current login details."</string>
    <string name="page1_choice1">Enter required information</string>
    <string name="page1_choice2">Ask supervisor about the email</string>

    <string name="page2">You leave work just after receiving the email to go
        home, traffic is not as bad as usual and you make it home in good time.
        For dinner you have a plate of lasagna and try to decide what to do for
        the evening.  </string>
    <string name="page2_choice1">Watch TV</string>
    <string name="page2_choice2">Play Video Games</string>

    <string name="page3">You enter your credentials into the web-page that the
        link directed you too. You filled it in quickly as you wanted to get
        home to watch "The Chase". Once home you relax for the evening and
        forget about the email. </string>
    <string name="page3_choice1">Go to bed early</string>
    <string name="page3_choice2">Stay up later</string>

    <string name="page4">At around 8 PM you decide it might be worth checking the
        email before going into work the next day. It reads,\n
        "Dear %1$s,\n It has come to our attention that the system that stores
        employee information requires an update so you will need to enter
        your login information into the linked form at the bottom
        of the email so that the system can be updated with your
        current login details."  </string>
    <string name="page4_choice1">Enter required information</string>
    <string name="page4_choice2">Deal with email at work tomorrow</string> <!--needs a solution-->

    <string name="page5">You get into work early to find that there has been
        a company wide phishing attack in which confidential company information
        was released. You begin to remember the email from yesterday and decide
        to take a closer look.</string>
    <string name="page5_choice1">Look at email again closely</string>
    <string name="page5_choice2">Tell supervisor about email</string>

    <string name="page6">You report the information to your supervisor and
        are informed that there has been no change to the company\'s storage
        system so therefore should not have received an email. You are
        advised to not input anything into the form. The supervisor alerts the
        security team within the company and an email is sent out alerting
        others who may have received the email. \n \n Good Job! You have saved
        the company\'s secrets.</string>

    <string name="page7">You look at the email again and see there are some signs
        that this email is not from a legitimate source.\n Some tell-tale signs of
        phishing can include an email address sent from a public domain such as
        "@gmail.com", no legitimate organisation will contact from an address like
        this. Another simple sign that an email may not be legitimate is that it is
        poorly written with even some potential misspellings including that of the
        domain name. \n
        \n
         Furthermore, the most common phishing emails will begin very generically as there
        are many emails sent at once to different people. This results in many phishing
        emails beginning with greetings such as “Dear Customer” or “Dear Employee”. However
        this does not mean that an email that does use your name is not a phishing email as
        there are many social engineering methods that an attacker could use to find your name,
        this is referred to as a spear-phishing attack so it is best to look for other signs also. \n
        \n
        Moreover, it is good to be on the look-out for emails that request urgent action is taken,
        such as emails warning that “your account will be closed” or “your account has been
        compromised” as these are used to generate a greater concern from the reader increasing the
        chance of the reader clicking a link. \n \n

        It is important to note that phishing scams are not only received through email. They can come
        through a variety of means, such as through messenger apps. It is important to make sure any message
        received in relation to anything about private credentials is legit, this can be done by contacting the
        sender company at an email or phone number you have used for legitimate contact before. Some sites that
        are commonly impersonated by scammers are Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn, with LinkedIn recording the most
        attempted phishing scams of the three.   \n \n

        Signs that you may be on a phishing website include a pop-up or pop-ups being displayed as
        soon as you enter the website. These pop-ups will usually request your username and
        password. If this happens it is best to leave the site without entering any information. \n
        \n
        Another way to check if a site is secure is to check the web address. It is worth having a
        closer look at things such as misspelled/incorrect company names. Additionally, when looking
        at the web address “https” is safer than “http”.
 </string>

    <string name="page8"> You go to a company mandated workshop to educate yourself on cyber-security, from this you learn some valuable things.  \n Some tell-tale signs of
        phishing can include an email address sent from a public domain such as
        "@gmail.com", no legitimate organisation will contact from an address like
        this. Another simple sign that an email may not be legitimate is that it is
        poorly written with even some potential misspellings including that of the
        domain name. \n
        \n
         Furthermore, the most common phishing emails will begin very generically as there
        are many emails sent at once to different people. This results in many phishing
        emails beginning with greetings such as “Dear Customer” or “Dear Employee”. However
        this does not mean that an email that does use your name is not a phishing email as
        there are many social engineering methods that an attacker could use to find your name,
        this is referred to as a spear-phishing attack so it is best to look for other signs also. \n
        \n
        Moreover, it is good to be on the look-out for emails that request urgent action is taken,
        such as emails warning that “your account will be closed” or “your account has been
        compromised” as these are used to generate a greater concern from the reader increasing the
        chance of the reader clicking a link. \n \n

        It is important to note that phishing scams are not only received through email. They can come
        through a variety of means, such as through messenger apps. It is important to make sure any message
        received in relation to anything about private credentials is legit, this can be done by contacting the
        sender company at an email or phone number you have used for legitimate contact before. Some sites that
        are commonly impersonated by scammers are Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn, with LinkedIn recording the most
        attempted phishing scams of the three.   \n \n

        Signs that you may be on a phishing website include a pop-up or pop-ups being displayed as
        soon as you enter the website. These pop-ups will usually request your username and
        password. If this happens it is best to leave the site without entering any information. \n
        \n
        Another way to check if a site is secure is to check the web address. It is worth having a
        closer look at things such as misspelled/incorrect company names. Additionally, when looking
        at the web address “https” is safer than “http”.</string>
    <string name="page9">You enter your credentials into the web-page that the
        link directed you too. You filled it in quickly as you wanted to get
        home to watch "The Chase". Once home you relax for the evening and
        forget about the email. </string>
    <string name="page9_choice1">Go to bed early</string>
    <string name="page9_choice2">Stay up later</string>

    <string name="startButton">Begin the game</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="phishing">Phishing Story</string>
    <string name="index_title">Choose an Option</string>
    <string name="malwareButtonText">Malware Story</string>
    <string name="attacker_story">Attacker Story</string>
    <string name="quizString">Quiz</string>

    <string name="page02">You arrive at work in the morning, after parking your car, while walking into work you discover a USB stick lying in the
        car park. You pick it up and take it into work with you.</string>
    <string name="page02_choice1">Plug it in</string>
    <string name="page02_choice2">Hand into reception</string>
    <string name="page12">You plug in the USB to your computer to see what’s on it and find nothing. You think someone may have just dropped a
        new USB. You decide to forget about it and continue your work for the day.</string>
    <string name="page12_choice1">Respond to emails</string>
    <string name="page12_choice2">Answer calls</string>
    <string name="page22">After handing the USB in to the reception you go to your desk to begin working. However, before starting you decide to
        check your email. Inside, there is an email offering you a discount on Netflix.</string>
    <string name="page22_choice1">Click the link</string>
    <string name="page22_choice2">Ignore the link</string>
    <string name="page32">You finish work for the morning and decide it would be a good time to stop and have lunch. You leave your desk to grab
        something to eat.</string>
    <string name="page32_choice1">Have a sandwich</string>
    <string name="page32_choice2">Have a bowl of soup</string>
    <string name="page42">The link takes you to a site that does not seem legit, you leave the site quickly after clicking on nothing within it.
        You go back to the work you were doing before.</string>
    <string name="page42_choice1">Respond to emails</string>
    <string name="page42_choice2">Answer calls</string>
    <string name="page52">Congratulations! You have avoided the cyber security threats that presented in this short story.</string>
    <string name="page62">You come back to your desk after lunch to discover that you are locked out of your system. The screen shows that you are
        required to send an amount of bitcoin to decrypt files on your computer. You wonder how this could have happened and realise the unidentified
        USB that was plugged into the computer.</string>
    <string name="page62_choice1">Tell your supervisor there is a problem</string>
    <string name="page62_choice2">Try and find information yourself</string>
    <string name="page72">You inform your boss about the attack on your system, he decides it would be good to hold a meeting with employees to discuss
        malware attacks. \n \n
        During the meeting a lot of useful information was given. \n \n
        Malicious software can come in many forms; these can range from not very to very dangerous. One type of malware that is not dangerous but
        annoying is adware. Adware displays ads on your computer and is very lucrative for the implementer of the adware. Another common type of
        malware is spyware which is software that tracks your internet activity in order to send advertising back to your system, this malware works
        well with adware. \n \n The most dangerous malware are trojans, trojans are written with the intention of discovering your financial information,
        taking over your computer’s system resources, and in larger systems creating a denial-of-service attack. A worm, another type of malware is a
        programme that replicates itself and destroys data and files on the computer. Worms work to “eat” the system operating files and data files
        until the drive is empty. \n \n A Rootkit, another type of malware is the hardest of all malware to detect and therefore remove; experts have
        even recommended wiping your hard drive and installing everything from scratch. Furthermore, a keylogger records everything typed on your PC,
        this allows for the keylogger to record sensitive information such as log-in names and passwords. Moreover, Ransomware is another type of
        malware that has been in the news in recent years. Ransomware locks you out of your system and requests payment to decrypt encrypted files,
        sometimes there will be a timer present on the screen and if payment is not made within the time the files will be deleted permanently.
        A virus is a contagious program or code that attaches itself to another piece of software, and then reproduces itself when that software is run. Most often this
        is spread by sharing software or files between computers. \n \n
        Malware can be given to a victim in many forms, these include Instant Messenger applications such as whatsApp, removable devices such as USB drives,
        fake software and untrusted sites and freeware. \n \n
        Malware attacks can be avoided or mitigated in many ways; one such simple solution is to update your software, i.e. whenever your
        OS prompts you for an update download it. It is also wise to update your browsers, antivirus software and firewall. Furthermore, securing
        your hardware is also important as electronics can be stolen, this can be solved by investing in hardware encryption and security keys.
        Furthermore, encrypting your data can stop hackers from understanding the information if they manage to get into your system.
    </string>
    <string name="page82">After searching online, you came across many useful websites and blogs. From them you learned many valuable points.
        \n \n Malware can come in many forms; these can range from not very to very dangerous. One type of malware that is not dangerous but annoying
        is adware. Adware displays ads on your computer and is very lucrative for the implementer of the adware. Another common type of malware is
        spyware which is software that tracks your internet activity in order to send advertising back to your system, this malware works well with
        adware. \n \n The most dangerous malware are trojans, trojans are written with the intention of discovering your financial information, taking
        over your computer’s system resources, and in larger systems creating a denial-of-service attack. A worm, another type of malware is a programme
        that replicates itself and destroys data and files on the computer. Worms work to “eat” the system operating files and data files until the
        drive is empty. \n \n A Rootkit, another type of malware is the hardest of all malware to detect and therefore remove; experts have even
        recommended wiping your hard drive and installing everything from scratch. Furthermore, a keylogger records everything typed on your PC,
        this allows for the keylogger to record sensitive information such as log-in names and passwords. Moreover, Ransomware is another type of
        malware that has been in the news in recent years. Ransomware locks you out of your system and requests payment to decrypt encrypted files,
        sometimes there will be a timer present on the screen and if payment is not made within the time the files will be deleted permanently.
        A virus is a contagious program or code that attaches itself to another piece of software, and then reproduces itself when that software is run. Most often this
        is spread by sharing software or files between computers. \n \n
        Malware can be given to a victim in many forms, these include Instant Messenger applications such as whatsApp, removable devices such as USB drives,
        fake software and untrusted sites and freeware. \n \n
        Malware attacks can be avoided or mitigated in many ways; one such simple solution is to update your software, i.e. whenever your OS
        prompts you for an update download it. It is also wise to update your browsers, antivirus software and firewall. Furthermore, securing your
        hardware is also important as electronics can be stolen, this can be solved by investing in hardware encryption and security keys.
        Furthermore, encrypting your data can stop hackers from understanding the information if they manage to get into your system.

    </string>

    <string name="page03">Cyber-attacks commonly begin with the attacker scoping out the target. This is called reconnaissance. In this phase you,
        the attacker, would identify the target or targets of the attack. It is also the stage where the existing security measures are determined
        and used to decide what attack is best used.</string>
    <string name="page03_choice1">Send a phishing email</string>
    <string name="page03_choice2">Use a spider programme</string>
    <string name="page13">You begin composing a phishing email to target all employees in an organisation, you decide the subject of the email
        should be…</string>
    <string name="page13_choice1">Account has been compromised</string>
    <string name="page13_choice2">You need to update your details</string>
    <string name="page23">After running the spider programme, you have found a vulnerability in the system that you can use to exploit and gain access
        to the underlying system. You decide it is a good place to insert some malware.</string>
    <string name="page23_choice1">Insert a remote access trojan</string>
    <string name="page23_choice2">Insert a Rootkit</string>
    <string name="page33">Once you have composed the phishing email you send it to all the employees at the company that you have access to. This type
        of attack does not have a lot of success however you only need one or two individuals within the company to give their details. With a
        successful attack you can get access to the company’s system. You use this to insert a…</string>
    <string name="page33_choice1">Insert a remote access trojan</string>
    <string name="page33_choice2">Insert a Rootkit</string>
    <string name="page43">Once you, the attacker, has established a connection to the internal network you seek to compromise additional systems
        and user accounts. This is commonly easy as the compromised account usually does not stand out as compromised.</string>
    <string name="page43_choice1">Steal sensitive data</string>
    <string name="page43_choice2">Encrypt data</string>
    <string name="page53">Hacking occurs in five stages, these are Reconnaissance, Scanning, Gaining Access, maintaining access and clearing tracks.
    Reconnaissance is the preparatory phase whereas much information is collected as possible about the target. The information is usually collected
    in three main groups, Network, Host and People involved. There are two types of reconnaissance involved Active and Passive. Active involves
    interacting directly with the target such as using tools to scan the target. Passive is trying to collect information about the target without
    directly accessing them such as collecting information from social media or websites accessible to the public. \n \n
    The scanning phase involves three types of scanning, Port scanning, which scans the target for things like open ports, live systems and services
    running on the host. Another type is vulnerability scanning which is used to check the target for weaknesses or vulnerabilities which can be
    exploited. This stage is usually done with automated tools. The final type of scanning is Network mapping, this type of scanning finds the
    topology of the network that shows routers, firewalls and any other host information. \n \n
    The third phase is gaining access, this phase is where an attacker actually breaks into the target system using various tools. After entering it
    is important to increase your privilege to administrator level so that applications that are needed can be installed and data can be modified
    or deleted. The fourth stage of the process is maintaining access, as once access is gained it is important to make sure the connection
    persists. This can be done by using trojans, rootkits or other malicious files. The aim of this stage is to maintain the access until the task
    the attacker wants to complete is finished. \n \n
    The final stage of the attack is to remove all evidence that you were in the system. This involves modifying, corrupting or deleting the values of
    Logs, modifying registry values and uninstalling all applications that were downloaded and deleting all folders that were created. \n \n
    Names are given to different types of hackers, there are white hat hackers who are ethical hackers who work within organisations to improve their
    security systems. White hat hackers are legally permitted to try and attack am organisations system. This type of hacker discloses every vulnerability
    that is discovered so that it can be changed. Black hat hackers on the other hand attempt to gain unauthorised entry into a system or network to exploit
    them for malicious reasons. Unlike the white hat hackers, black hat hackers have no permission for their activities and their goal is to steal information
    and/or cause as much damage to the system as possible. The final type is grey hat hackers, like black hat hackers, they have no permission to exploit
    networks. However, they do not exploit networks with malicious intent, disclosing any weaknesses they find to the owner of network. They may also extort
    the hacked offering to fix the problem for a fee.
    </string>
    <string name="page63">Hacking occurs in five stages, these are Reconnaissance, Scanning, Gaining Access, maintaining access and clearing tracks.
        Reconnaissance is the preparatory phase whereas much information is collected as possible about the target. The information is usually collected
        in three main groups, Network, Host and People involved. There are two types of reconnaissance involved Active and Passive. Active involves
        interacting directly with the target such as using tools to scan the target. Passive is trying to collect information about the target without
        directly accessing them such as collecting information from social media or websites accessible to the public. \n \n
        The scanning phase involves three types of scanning, Port scanning, which scans the target for things like open ports, live systems and services
        running on the host. Another type is vulnerability scanning which is used to check the target for weaknesses or vulnerabilities which can be
        exploited. This stage is usually done with automated tools. The final type of scanning is Network mapping, this type of scanning finds the
        topology of the network that shows routers, firewalls and any other host information. \n \n
        The third phase is gaining access, this phase is where an attacker actually breaks into the target system using various tools. After entering it
        is important to increase your privilege to administrator level so that applications that are needed can be installed and data can be modified
        or deleted. The fourth stage of the process is maintaining access, as once access is gained it is important to make sure the connection
        persists. This can be done by using trojans, rootkits or other malicious files. The aim of this stage is to maintain the access until the task
        the attacker wants to complete is finished. \n \n
        The final stage of the attack is to remove all evidence that you were in the system. This involves modifying, corrupting or deleting the values of
        Logs, modifying registry values and uninstalling all applications that were downloaded and deleting all folders that were created. \n \n
        Names are given to different types of hackers, there are white hat hackers who are ethical hackers who work within organisations to improve their
        security systems. White hat hackers are legally permitted to try and attack am organisations system. This type of hacker discloses every vulnerability
        that is discovered so that it can be changed. Black hat hackers on the other hand attempt to gain unauthorised entry into a system or network to exploit
        them for malicious reasons. Unlike the white hat hackers, black hat hackers have no permission for their activities and their goal is to steal information
        and/or cause as much damage to the system as possible. The final type is grey hat hackers, like black hat hackers, they have no permission to exploit
        networks. However, they do not exploit networks with malicious intent, disclosing any weaknesses they find to the owner of network. They may also extort
        the hacked offering to fix the problem for a fee.
    </string>
    <string name="highscore">Highscore: 0</string>
    <string name="start_quiz">Start Quiz</string>
    <string name="question">Question: 1/x</string>
    <string name="score">Score: 0</string>
    <string name="category">Category:</string>
    <string name="difficulty">Difficulty:</string>
    <string name="_00_30">00:30</string>
    <string name="here_will_be_the_question_text_nhere_will_be_the_question_text_nhere_will_be_the_question_text">Here will be the question text Here will be the question text Here will be the question text</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="option_3">Option 3</string>
    <string name="option_1">Option 1</string>
    <string name="option_2">Option 2</string>

</resources>
